Preliminary Inventory of the Center for Citizen Initiatives records
Hoover Institution Archives
Center for Citizen Initiatives records
1995-2007
2008C64
Hoover Institution Archives
142 manuscript boxes and 11 card file boxes (62 linear feet)
Meeting program materials, agenda, evaluation responses, reports, manuals, handbooks, correspondence, photographs, and video tapes, relating primarily to a productivity enhancement program to assist Russian entrepreneurs in improving productivity.
Center for Citizen Initiatives.
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 2008.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biographical/Historical Note
Private American organization promoting person-to-person contact between Americans and Russians.
Scope and Content of Collection
Meeting program materials, agenda, evaluation responses, reports, manuals, handbooks, correspondence, photographs, and video tapes, relating primarily to a productivity enhancement program to assist Russian entrepreneurs in improving productivity.
Business enterprises--Russia (Federation); Entrepreneurship--Russia (Federation); Russia (Federation)--Relations--United States.; United States--Relations--Russia (Federation); Video tapes.
- Manuals, handbooks, and promotional literature (Box 1-3)
- Quarterly reports (Box 4-6)
- Chronological Productivity Enhancement Program files (Box 7-21)
  - 1995-1997 (Box 7-9)
  - 1996-1997 (Box 10-12)
  - 1997-1998, 2001 (Box 13-15)
  - 1997-1998 (Box 16-18)
  - 1997-1998 evaluations (Box 19-21)
- Numerical Productivity Enhancement Program files, by delegation number (Box 22-108)
  - 1-99 (Box 22-24)
  - 100-123 (Box 25-27)
  - 124-150 (Box 28-30)
  - 152-172 (Box 31-33)
  - 173-192 (Box 34-36)
  - 193-216 (Box 37-39)
  - 217-242 (Box 40-42)
  - 243-267 (Box 43-45)
  - 268-280 (Box 46-48)
  - 281-294 (Box 49-51)
  - 295-310 (Box 52-54)
  - 312-327 (Box 55-57)
  - 328-340 (Box 58-60)
  - 342-352 (Box 61-63)
  - 353-364 (Box 64-66)
  - 365-378 (Box 67-69)
  - 379-388 (Box 70-72)
  - 389-401 (Box 73-75)
  - 402-418 (Box 76-78)
  - 419-429 (Box 79-81)
  - 430-445 (Box 82-84)
  - 446-459 (Box 85-87)
  - 460-478 (Box 88-90)
  - 479-498 (Box 91-93)
  - 499-515 (Box 94-96)
  - 517-530 (Box 97-99)
  - 531-551 (Box 100-102)
  - 552-567 (Box 103-105)
  - 569-600 (Box 106-108)
- Schultz Fellowship Fund files, 2000-2001 (Box 109-110)
- Schultz Fellowship Fund files, 2002 (Box 111)
- Soviets Meet Middle America video tapes (Box 112-113)
- Photographs (Box 114-125)
- Slides (Box 126-129)
- Russian art slides (Box 130)
- Incremental Materials (Box 131-153)